{
    "subject": "resource/Thunderbolt_and_Lightfoot",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_set_in_Montana",
    "human_readable": "Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is set in Montana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8392166495323181,
            "question": "How does the setting of Montana influence the characters and plot of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7186818718910217,
            "question": "If you visited Montana after watching Thunderbolt and Lightfoot, what places would you want to see?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.570380687713623,
            "question": "Where is the movie Thunderbolt and Lightfoot set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3730618357658386,
            "question": "Can you name a film set in Montana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3343765139579773,
            "question": "What state serves as the backdrop for the film Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2710786759853363,
            "question": "Is the movie Thunderbolt and Lightfoot a period piece?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2578727900981903,
            "question": "What is the overall atmosphere or mood created by the Montana setting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14225825667381287,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Montana that might appear in the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07816950976848602,
            "question": "Could this film have been set in a different location? Why or why not?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07352188974618912,
            "question": "What kind of stories are often told against the backdrop of Montana?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is set in Montana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3171_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could this film have been set in a different location? Why or why not?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3171_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks in Montana that might appear in the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3171_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall atmosphere or mood created by the Montana setting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3171_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3171_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information mentions that the film \"Thunderbolt and Lightfoot\" was shot entirely on location in Great Falls and the surrounding region of Montana, which supports the statement that the movie is set in Montana."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}